Tyme Bleyaert

Full-Stack .NET developer

Last update: February 7, 2024

Residence

LinkedIn

LinkedIn

Email

LinkedIn

LinkedIn

Up-to-date version of CV is available at

https://Tyme-Bleyaert.github.io/cv

I'm a full-stack .NET developer with over 2 years of experience. In the last years I got to work with Winforms, WPF, Angular, Blazor, ASP.Net, DevExtreme for front end, and for backend Windows services, Entity Framework, SQL and Blazor server.

Professional Experience

December 2023 - Present

De Jaeger Automation Byba

Senior full-stack .NET developer

July 2021 - November 2023

De Jaeger Automation Byba

Full-stack .NET developer



Working on the <u>ProSuite</u> framework. Developed a web based guidance application using Blazor and web API, ensuring scalability and performance. Improved stability and performance of the already existing framework and products.

Resposibilities:

- · Performing code reviews
- Mentoring junior developers
- · Promoting best coding practices
- Maintaining build and release pipelines

Reference(s):

Ronald Van Laerebeke (COO) <u>+32 (0)9 379 50 52</u>

Education

Game Development - Howest Kortrijk [2015 - 2016]
Web Development - Syntra West [2014 - 2015]
Accounting & Informatics - GO! Atheneum Maldegem [2014]

Skills



Additional Experience

Some of my interests and hobbies include working on my .NET library and providing assistance to other developers on open source projects (GitHub).

